A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Alphabetical, 1919-1929; 2
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - Canada, 1919-28 (Box 61, Folder 1482)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - Canada - Chengtu, 1920-28 (Box 61, Folder 1483)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - Canada - Chengtu, 1920-28 (Box 61, Folder 1484)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - Canada - Chengtu, 1920-28 (Box 61, Folder 1485)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - Canada - Chungchow, 1920-21 (Box 61, Folder 1486)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - Canada - Chungking, 1921-23 (Box 61, Folder 1487)
    - Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital - Canada - Tseliutsing, 1921-25 (Box 61, Folder 1488)
    - Metropolitan Library, 1926-28 (Box 61, Folder 1489)
    - Michigan Agricultural College, 1922 (Box 61, Folder 1490)
    - Michigan Health Department, 1925 (Box 61, Folder 1491)
    - Ava Milam, 1922 (Box 61, Folder 1492)
    - I. E. Miller, 1921-25 (Box 61, Folder 1493)
    - Ming Fu, 1926-27 (Box 61, Folder 1494)
    - Ming Tuh School, 1925 (Box 61, Folder 1495)
    - Minnesota Education Association, 1924 (Box 61, Folder 1496)
    - E. T. Mische, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 1497)
    - Mission Hospitals, 1916-26 (Box 62, Folder 1498)
    - Mission to Lepers, 1919-24 (Box 62, Folder 1499)
    - Missionary Review of the World, 1919-22 (Box 62, Folder 1500)
    - Missions, 1923 (Box 62, Folder 1501)
    - Mission Colleges, 1922-23 (Box 62, Folder 1502)
    - Keinosuke Miyairi, 1923 (Box 62, Folder 1503)
    - Mo Kwang Home, 1919-20 (Box 62, Folder 1504)
    - Model Prison, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 1505)
    - Modern Hospital, 1919-22 (Box 62, Folder 1506)
    - J. Howard Montgomery, 1923-25 (Box 62, Folder 1507)
    - Montreal General Hospital, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 1508)
    - H. B. Monturean, 1926 (Box 62, Folder 1509)
    - Alice Moore, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 1510)
    - Howard P. Moore, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 1511)
    - William Morton, 1923-24 (Box 62, Folder 1512)
    - Harris P. Mosher, 1927-28 (Box 62, Folder 1513)
    - Moukden Northeastern University, 1924-28 (Box 62, Folder 1514)
    - Mount Holyoke, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 1515)
    - Mount Sinai Hospital, 1919-27 (Box 62, Folder 1516)
    - John J. Mullowney, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 1517)
    - T. Murakami, 1923 (Box 62, Folder 1518)
    - Starr J. Murphy, 1919-21 (Box 62, Folder 1519)
    - Murphy and Dana, 1919-20 (Box 62, Folder 1520)
    - Museum of Comparative Zoology, 1925 (Box 62, Folder 1521)
    - L. G. Myers, 1921-26 (Box 62, Folder 1522)
    - Mysore Medical College, 1927 (Box 62, Folder 1523)
    - Nankai College, 1922-28 (Box 62, Folder 1524)
      Student unrest, political situation, endowment, gas plant
    - Nankai College, 1922-28 (Box 62, Folder 1525)
    - Nankai College, 1922-28 (Box 62, Folder 1526)
    - Nankai College, 1922-28 (Box 62, Folder 1527)
    - Nanking University Hospital, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 1528)
    - Nanyang College, 1923-27 (Box 62, Folder 1529)
    - Nation, 1927 (Box 62, Folder 1530)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Education, 1923-27 (Box 62, Folder 1531)
      See also National Association for the Promotion of Education
    - National Association for the Promotion of Education, 1922 (Box 62, Folder 1532)
    - National Christian Council, 1923-27 (Box 63, Folder 1533)
    - National College of Agriculture, 1923-24 (Box 63, Folder 1534)
    - National Committee for Legal Defense of Chinese, 1928 (Box 63, Folder 1535)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-28 (Box 63, Folder 1536)
    - National Conference of Social Work, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1537)
    - National Educational Reform Association, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1538)
    - National Health Association of China, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1539)
    - National Health Council, 1922-27 (Box 63, Folder 1540)
    - National Medical Association of China, 1920-28 (Box 63, Folder 1541)
    - National Medical College, 1922-23 (Box 63, Folder 1542)
    - National Medical Missionary Association, 1922-25 (Box 63, Folder 1543)
    - National Normal University, 1925-27 (Box 63, Folder 1544)
    - National Research Council, 1922-27 (Box 63, Folder 1545)
    - National Southeastern University, 1921-27 (Box 63, Folder 1546)
      Political situation, biology, physics, chemistry, student unrest, teacher strike, Government University
    - National Southeastern University, 1921-27 (Box 63, Folder 1547)
    - National Southeastern University, 1921-27 (Box 63, Folder 1548)
    - National Southeastern University, 1921-27 (Box 63, Folder 1549)
    - National Southeastern University, 1921-27 (Box 63, Folder 1550)
    - National Southeastern University, 1921-27 (Box 63, Folder 1551)
    - National Student Council of the Episcopal Church, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 1552)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1923-26 (Box 63, Folder 1553)
    - National Women's Christian Temperance Union, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1554)
    - Native Races Anti-Liquor Traffic Commission, 1923 (Box 63, Folder 1555)
    - Naval Medical College, 1921 (Box 63, Folder 1556)
    - Near East Relief, 1924-27 (Box 63, Folder 1557)
    - Oscar Nelson, 1919 (Box 63, Folder 1558)
    - New York Department of Health (Box 63, Folder 1559)
    - New York Hospital, 1923 (Box 63, Folder 1560)
    - New York Post Graduate Hospital, 1926-28 (Box 63, Folder 1561)
    - New York University, 1920-24 (Box 63, Folder 1562)
    - Newark Museum Association, 1923-24 (Box 63, Folder 1563)
    - Henry W. Newman, 1919-25 (Box 63, Folder 1564)
    - Arthur Newholme, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1565)
    - Miriam Nieh, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1566)
    - Frank L. Norris, 1920 (Box 64, Folder 1567)
    - North China American School, 1922 (Box 64, Folder 1568)
    - North China Medical School for Women, 1922-23 (Box 64, Folder 1569)
    - North China Union Language School, 1919-24 (Box 64, Folder 1570)
      LSRM, Advisory Committee, teach the Chinese language to foreigners
    - North China Union Language School, 1919-24 (Box 64, Folder 1571)
    - Norwegian Lutheran Church of America, 1922-23 (Box 64, Folder 1572)
    - Norwegian Mission Hospital - Kalgon, 1926-27 (Box 64, Folder 1573)
    - Norwegian Mission Hospital - Kwangchow, 1922-25 (Box 64, Folder 1574)
    - Norwegian Mission Hospital - Yiyang, 1919-25 (Box 64, Folder 1575)
    - Northwestern University, 1921-27 (Box 64, Folder 1576)
    - Nurses Association of China, 1922-27 (Box 64, Folder 1577)
    - Clara Nutting, 1921-27 (Box 64, Folder 1578)
    - Vong Sung Nyi, 1919-23 (Box 64, Folder 1579)
    - Henry R. O'Brien, 1920-24 (Box 64, Folder 1580)
    - I. Ogawa, 1920 (Box 64, Folder 1581)
    - Ohio State University, 1919-25 (Box 64, Folder 1582)
    - Ohio Wesleyan University, 1925 (Box 64, Folder 1583)
    - Oliver Jones Dormitory, 1922 (Box 64, Folder 1584)
    - Opium, 1920-26 (Box 64, Folder 1585)
    - E. I. Osgood, 1925 (Box 64, Folder 1586)
    - M. A. Oudin, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 1587)
    - Leonard Outhwaite, 1923-27 (Box 64, Folder 1588)
    - Louis Palen, 1922 (Box 64, Folder 1589)
    - Pan Pacific Conference, 1925-28 (Box 64, Folder 1590)
    - Pao Lee Hospital, 1919-25 (Box 64, Folder 1591)
    - Paris Office, 1924-28 (Box 64, Folder 1592)
    - Pasteur Institute of Saigon, 1924 (Box 64, Folder 1593)
    - Pathological Institute, 1924 (Box 64, Folder 1594)
    - Francis W. Peabody, 1919-26 (Box 64, Folder 1595)
    - Richard M. Pearce, 1921-27 (Box 64, Folder 1596)
    - Esther Peh, 1926 (Box 65, Folder 1597)
    - Pennsylvania State Board of Medical Education, 1926 (Box 65, Folder 1598)
    - Pennsylvania State College, 1924 (Box 65, Folder 1599)
    - Peking Academy, 1923 (Box 65, Folder 1600)
    - Peking American School, 1920-27 (Box 65, Folder 1601)
      American children in China
    - Peking American School, 1920-27 (Box 65, Folder 1602)
    - Peking American School, 1920-27 (Box 65, Folder 1603)
    - Peking American School, 1920-27 (Box 65, Folder 1604)
    - Peking Language School, 1919 (Box 65, Folder 1605)
    - Peking Leader, 1924-26 (Box 65, Folder 1606)
    - Peking Magazine, 1926-27 (Box 65, Folder 1607)
    - Peking National Medical School, 1921-22 (Box 65, Folder 1608)
    - Peking National University, 1920-25 (Box 65, Folder 1609)
    - Peking Normal University, 1924 (Box 65, Folder 1610)
    - Peking Obstetrical Hospital, 1925 (Box 65, Folder 1611)
    - Peking Office, April-September 1927 (Box 65, Folder 1612)
      Duplicates of material in subject files, cross-references; political situation, PUMC, journals, public health, pharmacy, famine relief, universities and appropriations, transitional policies, parasitology, emergency fund, midwifery, anthropology, fellowships. Archibald P. Chien, W. S. Carter, N. Gist Gee
    - Peking Office, April-September 1927 (Box 65, Folder 1613)
    - Peking Office, April-September 1927 (Box 65, Folder 1614)
    - Peking Office, April-September 1927 (Box 65, Folder 1615)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1616)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1617)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1618)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1619)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1620)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1621)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1622)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1623)
    - Peking Office, October 1927-28 (Box 66, Folder 1624)
    - Peking Union Church, 1921-23 (Box 66, Folder 1625)
    - Peking Union Medical College, 1918 - March 1919 (Box 66, Folder 1626)
      Construction, supplies, staff
    - Peking Union Medical College, 1918 - March 1919 (Box 66, Folder 1627)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1628)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1629)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1630)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1631)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1632)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1633)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1634)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1635)
    - Peking Union Medical College, April 1919-26 (Box 67, Folder 1636)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Advisory Committee, 1925 (Box 67, Folder 1637)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Carbon Dioxide Plant, 1924-25 (Box 67, Folder 1638)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Charter, 1928 (Box 67, Folder 1639)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1640)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1641)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1642)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1643)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1644)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1645)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1646)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1647)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1648)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction, 1921-28 (Box 68, Folder 1649)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Costs, 1923-26 (Box 68, Folder 1650)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Specification, 1926 (Box 68, Folder 1651)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Pamphlets (Box 69, Folder 1652)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Gas Plant, 1922-24 (Box 69, Folder 1653)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Hixon Electric Company, 1919-24 (Box 69, Folder 1654)
      See also PUMC-Thermostatic Control
    - Peking Union Medical College - Hygiene (Box 69, Folder 1655)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Insurance and Pension, 1919-20 (Box 69, Folder 1656)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Neurology, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 1657)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Power Plant, 1926 (Box 69, Folder 1658)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Property, 1923-26 (Box 69, Folder 1659)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Purchasing Agent, 1919 (Box 69, Folder 1660)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Refinite Plant, 1920-24 (Box 69, Folder 1661)
      See also PUMC-Water Softener and PUMC-Water Supply System, Water Softening
    - Peking Union Medical College - Refinite Plant, 1920-24 (Box 69, Folder 1662)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Refinite Plant, 1920-24 (Box 69, Folder 1663)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Refinite Plant Pamphlets (Box 69, Folder 1664)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Refridgeration, 1921-26 (Box 69, Folder 1665)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Religion, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 1666)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Staff, 1927 (Box 69, Folder 1667)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Thermostatic Control, 1921-22 (Box 69, Folder 1668)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Water Softener, 1925 (Box 70, Folder 1669)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Water Supply System, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 1670)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1671)
      Union university, political situation, buildings, curriculum, staff
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1672)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1673)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1674)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1675)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1676)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1677)
    - Peking University, 1919-25 (Box 70, Folder 1678)
    - Peking Women's University, 1925 (Box 70, Folder 1679)
    - John Pelenyi, 1923 (Box 70, Folder 1680)
    - W. W. Peter, 1919-22 (Box 70, Folder 1681)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, 1919-27 (Box 70, Folder 1682)
    - Peters Photographic Expedition, 1920 (Box 70, Folder 1683)
    - Thomas Peterson, 1923 (Box 70, Folder 1684)
    - Philadelphia College of Pharmacy and Science, 1925 (Box 70, Folder 1685)
    - Philadelphia General Hospital, 1921-26 (Box 70, Folder 1686)
    - Philanthropy Fund, 1924 (Box 70, Folder 1687)
    - Ludwig Pick, 1927 (Box 70, Folder 1688)
    - C. Ping, 1923-28 (Box 70, Folder 1689)
    - Edwin H. Place, 1920-26 (Box 70, Folder 1690)
    - Plague Prevention, 1921 (Box 70, Folder 1691)
    - G. A. Plimpton, 1920-25 (Box 70, Folder 1692)
    - Police Systems, 1922 (Box 71, Folder 1693)
    - Political Situation, 1924-27 (Box 71, Folder 1694)
      Wounded relief, anti-foreign, anti-Christian agitation, student unrest and demonstration, student union, labor unrest, industrial disputes and strikes, racial animosity, banditry, tariff, Chinese political factions
    - Political Situation, 1924-27 (Box 71, Folder 1695)
    - Political Situation, 1924-27 (Box 71, Folder 1696)
    - Political Situation, 1924-27 (Box 71, Folder 1697)
    - Political Situation, 1924-27 (Box 71, Folder 1698)
    - Polytechnic Institute, 1920 (Box 71, Folder 1699)
    - Dr. Pool, 1927 (Box 71, Folder 1700)
    - Lucius Porter, 1923-24 (Box 71, Folder 1701)
    - Porter Middle School, 1925 (Box 71, Folder 1702)
    - Post Graduate Hospital and Middle School, 1919-22 (Box 71, Folder 1703)
    - Post Graduate Medical Training, 1922 (Box 71, Folder 1704)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1919 (Box 71, Folder 1705)
      Political situation, Japanese earthquake, famine relief, exchange
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1919 (Box 71, Folder 1706)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1919 (Box 71, Folder 1707)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1919 (Box 71, Folder 1708)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1919 (Box 71, Folder 1709)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Changteh, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1710)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Changteh, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1711)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Changteh, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1712)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Chefoo, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1713)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Chefoo, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1714)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Chefoo, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1715)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Hengchow, 1919 (Box 72, Folder 1716)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Hwaiyuen, 1919-28 (Box 72, Folder 1717)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Kachek, 1919-27 (Box 72, Folder 1718)
      Hookworm
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Kachek, 1919-27 (Box 72, Folder 1719)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - J. G. Kerr Hospital, 1927 (Box 72, Folder 1720)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Korea, 1922-23 (Box 72, Folder 1721)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Paotingfu, 1919-23 (Box 72, Folder 1722)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Paotingfu, 1919-23 (Box 72, Folder 1723)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Paotingfu, 1924-28 (Box 73, Folder 1724)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Peking, 1920-28 (Box 73, Folder 1725)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Shuntefu, 1919-28 (Box 73, Folder 1726)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Shuntefu, 1919-28 (Box 73, Folder 1727)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Weihsien, 1922-26 (Box 73, Folder 1728)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, North - Yihsien, 1920-25 (Box 73, Folder 1729)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1730)
      Union University, political situation, endowment, student unrest, Boxer indemnity, food research, merger.
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1731)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1732)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1733)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1734)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1735)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1919-23 (Box 73, Folder 1736)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1737)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1738)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1739)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1740)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1741)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1742)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1743)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1744)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1745)
    - Presbyterian Church - Shantung Christian University, 1924-28 (Box 74, Folder 1746)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States, South, 1919-27 (Box 75, Folder 1747)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, South - Kashing, 1919-25 (Box 75, Folder 1748)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, South - Soochow, 1920-26 (Box 75, Folder 1749)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, South - Taichow, 1922-28 (Box 75, Folder 1750)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, South - Tsingkiangpu, 1920-27 (Box 75, Folder 1751)
    - Presbyterian Church, Canada, 1920-25 (Box 75, Folder 1752)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, Canada - Changtecho, 1920-23 (Box 75, Folder 1753)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, Canada - Hwaikingfu, 1922-27 (Box 75, Folder 1754)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, Canada - Kai Kwong, 1925 (Box 75, Folder 1755)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, Canada - Lungchingtsun, 1921-27 (Box 75, Folder 1756)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, Canada - Weihei, 1923-24 (Box 75, Folder 1757)
    - Presbyterian Church, England, 1924 (Box 75, Folder 1758)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, England - Chuanchowfu, 1919-20 (Box 75, Folder 1759)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, England - Swatow, 1919-25 (Box 75, Folder 1760)
    - Presbyterian Mission Hospital, England - Wukingfu, 1923 (Box 75, Folder 1761)
    - Presbyterian Hospital, 1924-26 (Box 75, Folder 1762)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1921-23 (Box 75, Folder 1763)
      Cross-references, duplicate of material in subject files; fellowships and policy, university pre-medical programs, summer institutes and science teaching, medical and scientific journals, visiting professors, Peking Union Medical College, political situation, indemnity fund, anti-Christian feeling, student and labor unrest, mission schools, educational standards and requirements.
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1921-23 (Box 75, Folder 1764)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1921-23 (Box 75, Folder 1765)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1921-23 (Box 75, Folder 1766)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1921-23 (Box 75, Folder 1767)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1924-28 (Box 76, Folder 1768)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1924-28 (Box 76, Folder 1769)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1924-28 (Box 76, Folder 1770)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1924-28 (Box 76, Folder 1771)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1924-28 (Box 76, Folder 1772)
    - Pre-Medical Examination, 1924-28 (Box 76, Folder 1773)
    - Preventative Medicine, 1922 (Box 76, Folder 1774)
    - Maurice Price, 1924 (Box 76, Folder 1775)
    - Theodore H. Price, 1923 (Box 76, Folder 1776)
    - Princeton in Peking, 1922-27 (Box 76, Folder 1777)
    - Princeton School of Political and Social Science, 1925 (Box 76, Folder 1778)
    - Princeton University, 1920-27 (Box 76, Folder 1779)
    - Proxies, 1919-24 (Box 76, Folder 1780)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1919-28 (Box 76, Folder 1781)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1919-28 (Box 76, Folder 1782)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Anking, 1918-23 (Box 76, Folder 1783)
      Political situation, x-ray
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Anking, 1918-23 (Box 76, Folder 1784)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Anking, 1924-27 (Box 77, Folder 1785)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Anking, 1924-27 (Box 77, Folder 1786)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Pakhoi, 1919-20 (Box 77, Folder 1787)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Shanghai, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1788)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Wuchangi, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1789)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Wuchangi, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1790)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Yunnanfu, 1919-20 (Box 77, Folder 1791)
    - Protestant Episcopal Mission Hospital - Boone University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1792)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1793)
      Political situation, student unrest, indemnity funds, exchange
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1794)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1795)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1796)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1797)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1798)
    - Protestant Episcopal Church - St. John's University, 1919-28 (Box 77, Folder 1799)
    - S. O. Pruitt, 1927 (Box 78, Folder 1800)
    - Alfonso Pruneda, 1922-23 (Box 78, Folder 1801)
    - Public Health, 1919-23 (Box 78, Folder 1802)
    - Public Health, 1919-23 (Box 78, Folder 1803)